美丽的人们大家好，欢迎收看这个视频。
Hello the beautiful people and welcome to this video.
我们将使用您自己的运行特定风格的Linux虚拟机进行设置
We're going to be getting you set up with your very own Linux virtual machine running a specific flavor
被称为Buntu的Linux的。
of Linux called a buntu.
所以Linux的风格在Linux行话中被称为发行版，我们将为您设置
So flavors of Linux are called distributions in the Linux lingo and we're going to be getting you set
为您的虚拟机器虚拟机提供Linux的Ubuntu发行版。
up with Ubuntu distribution of Linux for your virtual box virtual machines.
所以我们要做的就是总是带着一个项目符号走到窗口，从.com下载它的
So we're going to do is always a head over to the window with a bullet to dot com for download for its
最后一个桌面。
last desktop.
我将在资源部分放置一个链接，用于此视频，或者您可以直接转到
I will be putting a link in the resources section and for this video or you could just head over to
你最喜欢的搜索引擎和搜索按钮下载，它将是第一件事
your favorite search engine and search for a button to download and it'll be the first thing that comes
当你点击它的时候，你会发现一个像这样的页面。
up and when you click on it you'll find a page that looks like this.
现在，我们不希望您这样做，我们将为您提供多个选项，您可以选择使用哪种版本的Buntu
Now we don't want you to do and is going to give you multiple options of what version of a buntu you
想要下载。
want to download.
但我希望您点击最新的选项。
But I want you to click on the most up to date option.
举个例子，我这里有，我去过17.10。
So for example here I've got I've been to seventeen point ten.
现在有一件有趣的事情，你实际上可以告诉我们Buntu发行版是什么时候发布的，只需看一下
Now one interesting thing you can actually tell when the buntu releases were released by just looking
从版本号上，Sahira可以看出它是在2000年发布的，在第10个月发布了17个月，这将
at the version number Sahira can tell that it was released in 2000 and 17 in the tenth month which would
就是这里的十月。
be October of here.
例如，我可以看到这是在2000年发布的，16年是在第四个月发布的，这将是
For example I can see that this was released in 2000 and 16 in the fourth month which is going to be
四月。
April.
因此，更新的版本号越多，就意味着它们发布的时间越晚。
So the more up to date version numbers mean they were released later on.
好的。
OK.
所以我们要做的就是点击它。
So what we're going to do is we're going to click in it will.
任何人都会点击17：10，但你只需点击对你来说最新的内容，它就会
Anyone going to click on to 17:10 but you just click on whatever is most up to date for you it will
不会影响您的课程体验，无论如何，整个费用对您来说都是一样的
not affect your experience of the course the entire cost will be the same for you regardless whatever
您可以选择最新的版本，但您也可以选择最新的版本。
version you pick but you might as well have the most up to date version.
所以当你点击下载时，它会打开另一个页面，在那里它会要求我提供几笔捐款
So when you click download and it can open up another page where it's going to ask me for a few donations
但我要说的是，很遗憾，我今天不会在这里捐钱，我会
but I'm going to say unfortunately that I'm not going to donate any money here today and I'm going to
将被带到下载位置。
be taken to the download.
但是你可以随心所欲地做任何你想做的事。
And but you feel free to do whatever you want to do.
好的。
OK.
然后它会开始将所谓的磁盘镜像文件下载到我的计算机上，然后我会
And then it's going to start to download what's called a disk image file to my computer and I'm going
为我自己单击并保存在Downloads文件夹中。
to click and save it in the Downloads folder for myself.
你可以随心所欲地下载。
You can download it wherever you want.
您会注意到下载开始了。
And you'll notice that a download starts to begin.
现在这些ISO文件过去是10个，通常是相当大的，通常在千兆字节的数量级上，所以
Now these ISO files used to be 10 usually tend to be quite large usually on the order of gigabytes so
您可以在这里看到这是1.4 GB大小。
you can see here that this is 1.4 gigabytes in size.
因此，这可能需要相当长的一段时间，这取决于您的互联网有多快。
So this might take quite a while depending on how quick your Internet is.
现在你必须等待它继续下载，我要做的是我要把
Now you have to wait for that to go ahead and downloads what I'm going to do is I'm going to cut the
视频在这里。
video here.
我下载后会回来的，所以只要耐心点，她就不会真的
I'm going to come back when it is downloaded so just be patient with it she won't ever have to really
再来一次。
do it again.
所以，一旦它完成了，它就完成了。
And so once it's done it's done.
因此，只需等待该内容下载，然后取消暂停视频，即可继续使用睡觉
So just wait for that thing to download and then unpause the video to follow through with the rest of
设置好了。
the set up.
好的，下载尚未完成，现在我可以继续安装虚拟机，这样您
OK so the download has gone incompleted and now I can go ahead and install the virtual machine so you
我可以看到，我们已经将此磁盘映像文件保存在我的下载文件夹中。
can see that we've got this disk image file saved in my downloads folder.
有了这一点，我们将有一个开放的虚拟盒子，虚拟盒子。
And with that there we're going to go had an open up virtual box virtual box.
在这里您可以设置虚拟机并尝试运行，并且您可以拥有多个交换机
This is where you can set up virtual machines and try to run and you can have more than one switch is
正在创建新的虚拟机。
going to create a new virtual machine.
我要称它为Buntu，因为我很有想象力，你可以看到它找到了
I'm going to call it a buntu because I am imaginative and call it and you can see it's it's found the
类型是Linux和Buntu 64位，这就是我的那个。
type which is Linux and a buntu 64 bit which is which is what my one was.
如果你的下载是32位的，那么继续点击到32位。
And if yours was a 32 bit download then go ahead and click to 32 bit.
但我认为默认情况下应该是64位，所以我就不说了。
But I think by default it should be a 64 bit so I'll leave it at that.
现在我下一个被击中，它将询问我要分配的内存或RAM的大小(以MB为单位
Now I get hit next and it's going to ask me for the amount of memory or RAM in megabytes to be allocated
到虚拟机。
to the virtual machine.
这里需要注意的重要一点是，这仅在虚拟机运行时分配
Now an important thing to note here that this is only allocated when the virtual machine is running
当您关闭虚拟机时启用虚拟。
when you turn the virtue when you close a virtual machine.
它会的。
It will.
它将被归还给主机。
It will be given back to the host computer.
所以不要太担心这个，只要给它一个慷慨的数额，让我们说，大约，我们说
So don't worry about this too much just give it a generous amount so let's say up to about let's say
大约四分之三或80%的果岭距离你不想一直走到这里
about three quarters or 80 percent of the green distance you don't want to go all the way up to here
因为这可能会使您的系统出现一点卡顿和抖动。
because this might make your system stutter a bit and jittery a bit.
所以只要走到果岭的大部分路，直到果岭的尽头，但不能一直走到果岭的尽头。
So just take it most of the way up to the green to the end of the green but not all the way.
所以在那里留出一些缓冲空间。
So leave some buffer room there.
好的，那我就到此为止了。
OK so I'm going to leave it at that.
照我说的做。
Do it by.
这不是一门完美的科学。
This isn't a perfect science.
你可以想象，到那时，你会问你关于硬盘的问题，那就是
Just go ahead and do it by then is going to ask you about a hard disk now that you can imagine is that
这个虚拟机认为它是一台计算机，而计算机需要一个硬盘空间。
this virtual machine is thinks that it's a computer and a computer needs a hard drive space.
好的。
OK.
所以我们要做的是创建一个虚拟的硬盘，这个虚拟的盒子就是这台机器
So what we're doing is we're creating an imaginary hard drive that this virtual box is this which machine
会认为这是一个真正的硬盘。
is going to think is a real hard drive.
但它实际上只是我们实际电脑上保存的一个文件。
But it's actually just a file saved on our actual computer.
好的。
OK.
所以我们现在能做的就是创建一个虚拟硬盘。
So what we can do is we get to create a virtual hard disk now.
这会创建它，它会告诉您希望它是什么类型，只需将其作为第一个选项保留为虚拟的
So this creates it and it says what type do you want it to be just leave it as the first option a virtual
将磁盘映像装箱，或者就这样放在那里。
box disk image or leave it just like that.
然后它会说你想让它成为。
And then it's going to say do you want it to be.
您希望文件日期是动态分配还是固定大小和动态分配方式
Do you want the file dates to be dynamically allocated or fixed size and dynamically allocated means
当数据填满我想象中的硬盘时，火将变得更大且大小固定
that when when the data fills up on my imaginary harddrive the fire will get bigger and fix size means
不管是什么大小，文件都会是这个大小。
that the file will be that size no matter what.
即使出于效率的考虑，它基本上是空的，我们也只需要动态分配它即可。
Even if it's basically empty for efficiency sake let's just have it dynamically allocated.
然后，您可以随心所欲地将其命名，并通过单击此箭头将其存储在您想要的任何位置
And then you can call it whatever you want and store it wherever you want by clicking this this arrow
此处更改您想要保存它的位置，但如果您不特别需要，请将其保留为默认位置
here to change where you want to save it but just leave it as the default if you don't particularly
速度快，这不是很重要，你给它多大的尺寸，我倾向于给我的20
fast and it doesn't really matter massively and how much size you give it I tend to just give my 20
千兆字节通常是绰绰有余的。
gigabytes that's usually more than enough.
但是你可以，你可以选择适合你的。
But you can you can just choose what's all right for you.
你知道，只要你有超过一两千兆字节的东西，你就应该完全没问题。
It's you know as long as you've got something above one or two gigabytes you should be absolutely fine.
因此，我将有20 GB的空间用作虚拟硬盘，然后我将单击
So so I'm just going to have 20 gigabytes there for it as an imaginary hard disk and I'm going to click
创建。
Create.
好的。
OK.
所以我们就快到了，我们非常非常接近。
So we're almost there and we're very very close.
我们要做的就是单击设置以设置更多内容，以确保
We've got to do is click on settings to set up a few more things so to make sure that are to make sure
我们的虚拟机的功率只是稍微高一点。
that our virtual machine has just a bit more power.
我们要做的是单击设置，进入系统，然后单击处理器处理
What we're going to do is we're going to click on settings go to System and click Proceso the processor
制表符，如果您有两个原因，则将其增加到两个原因。
tab and increase this to two cause if you have them.
所以这里有两个处理器，或者一直到绿灯的尽头。
So two processors or up to the end of the green here.
因此，我要做的基本上就是让虚拟机具有更高的性能。
So what I'm going to do that just basically allows the virtual machine to just have that bit more performance.
好的。
OK.
除了您单击存储时，还有最后一件事要做之外，其他一切都应该是一样的。
And everything else should be the same except when you click on storage there's one final thing to do.
在存储上，这就是我们要插入磁盘映像的地方，因此您可以想象
So on storage This is where we're going to basically insert that disk image so you can imagine that
虚构的计算机从豆瓣Buntu映像引导到一台真实的计算机。
the imaginary computer booting from that Douban buntu image into a real computer.
这有点让人困惑，不过请跟我来，点击存储，然后你会在这里看到这一点
It's a bit confusing but just follow with me it's click on storage then you'll see this bit here where
它显示控制器ID，并且它将有一个显示为空的磁盘。
it says controller ID and it will have a disk that says empty.
好的。
OK.
单击，然后单击顶部的这张桌子右击，它将显示选择虚拟光学
So click then click on this desk at the top right click that and it will say choose virtual optical
磁盘文件显示单击锁定，然后我们将转到我的下载文件夹，并单击Ribband至17点
disk file says Click lock then we'll go to my downloads folder and click on ribband to seventeen point
我们下载的10个磁盘映像或您下载的任何磁盘映像版本
ten disk image that we downloaded or whatever disk image version that you downloaded you're able to
版本单击打开。
version click open.
现在一切都准备好了。
And now that's that's all set up.
单击确定。
Click OK.
我们基本上都可以出发了。
And we're basically all good to go.
所有这些都准备好了，在下一个视频中，我们将带您一览无余。
So that's all set up ready to go and in the next video we're going to run you through.
安装的最后一步是在实际的Buntu机器启动时对其进行设置。
And the final bit of the installation which is setting up the actual buntu machine when it boots up.
好了，我会在下一个视频中见到你。
So for all that goodness I'll see you in the next video.